<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on t3mujinpack</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on t3mujinpack</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 11:11:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>t3mujinpack 0.6.0 is out</title>
      <link>/2020/04/30/t3mujinpack-0.6.0-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/04/30/t3mujinpack-0.6.0-is-out/</guid>
      <description>A long overdue update of t3mujinpack! I was meant to release this version to match the launch of Darktable 3, but a bug related with the edit of existing styles prevented me from editing them, and thus had to wait for Darktable 3.0.1 to be released to wrap this up.
As you might expect from such a huge amount of time since the last release, there are a few updates. First of all, most of existing styles were re-tested and, for many, re-tweaked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>t3mujinpack 0.5.0 is out</title>
      <link>/2019/01/20/t3mujinpack-0.5.0-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/20/t3mujinpack-0.5.0-is-out/</guid>
      <description>After the release of version 0.4.0 it was brought to my attention that the “Portras” NC/UC/VC were a bit off. And it was true, I did some changes on those but you can say the Quality Control was severely lacking… Not an excuse, but that’s a problem of using some styles more others.
So the focus change on this version was getting those styles to work properly, starting almost from scratch, as it was suppose to happened in the previous version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>t3mujinpack 0.4.0 is out</title>
      <link>/2018/07/30/t3mujinpack-0.4.0-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/30/t3mujinpack-0.4.0-is-out/</guid>
      <description>The main purpose of my film emulation presets is to be used in my own processing. This may sound redundant and pointless but essentially is a personal project, and that means I end up using some styles more than others, either because I really dig a film’s look and use it often (Kodachrome!…) or at a given moment I’m exploring a specific look for a given essay. That was the case for some Fuji emulations, Provia is my default style, the one I select when I don’t want anything (also because it’s the default on my cameras), but it’s not necessarily the same for others, like Astia or the Pro, although lovely, I didn’t find a way to fit them in my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>t3mujinpack 0.3.0 is out</title>
      <link>/2017/03/26/t3mujinpack-0.3.0-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 11:11:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/26/t3mujinpack-0.3.0-is-out/</guid>
      <description>A new release of t3mujinpack (the Darktable film emulation presets) is ready and available for all. Unlike the previous one, where most emulations were updated in a big way, this is a smaller release, but one with new things nevertheless.
With the regular use while processing my photos (like the above photo using Kodachrome 200, taken on a recent flea market photowalk) some presets received some fine tweaks, and in the end it’s no surprise some of these changes were in two of my most used preset groups: Fuji Provia and Kodak Kodachrome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
